[
  {
    "answer": "stopping smoking is about will power and being steadfast. you can stop safely by having bupropion or nicotine patch cover initially in consult with a doctor. contact an addiction clinic near you. wishing you best of health thanks",
    "question": "how do i stop smoking now",
    "url": "http://ehealthforum.com/health/stop-smoking-question-t462882.html",
    "tags": [
      "addiction",
      "stop smoking"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "hello this sounds quite unfamiliar that due to no reason at this age you have no cycle for last three months. pregnancy is surely a remote possibility as there was a tubal ligation. the endometriosis is also unlikely could cause stoppage of cycle. you definitely need some hormonal tests like thyroid or prolactin to know the balance inside as well as an withdrawal bleeding. meet your doctor for an evaluation.",
    "question": "i had a tubaligation 4 years ago and also have a minor case of endometriosis i am only 27 and my period stopped completely 3 months ago no more spotting in between nothing i am not stressed no change in daily habits diet weight nothing all urine pregnancy tests have been negative what could be wrong with me?",
    "url": "http://ehealthforum.com/health/endometriosis-question-t494011.html",
    "tags": [
      "pregnancy",
      "diet",
      "endometriosis"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "extra caffeine can cause gastric discomfort the pain of which can be felt at one side of breast mostly left side but right also is possible and some times whole chest. get evaluated for any local pathology like mastitis. i hope it helps. stay in touch with your healthcare provider for further guidance as our answers are just for education and counselling purposes and cannot be an alternative to actual visit to a doctor. take care khan",
    "question": "could extra caffeine consumption be a cause of mild unilateral breast tenderness?",
    "url": "http://ehealthforum.com/health/caffeine-consumption-causing-breast-tenderness-t505151.html",
    "tags": [
      "breast cancer",
      "cancer",
      "breasts"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "hello thanks for submitting your question here. as per the description you have undergone repeated surgery for ovarian torsion where the ovary is preserved. this sounds a bit different as in torsion it is a dictum to remove the whole ovary. now as you are having recurrent pain from the ovaries you need an obg consultation right now. there may be possibility of endometriosis which might present with similar feature. you need to have the biopsy of previous operation and only after few blood tests and clinical examination; a definite opinion can be formed. sincerely dr bhattacharyya",
    "question": "hello- i am a 24 year old female 5\"4 & 115 lb & was diagnosed with pcos at 19. i've always been active & extremely healthy. spironolactone & an iud helped with acne & pain but in 2013 i had an ovarian torsion requiring surgery & they saved my right ovary. i began having hair loss from telogen effogen & reoccurant yeast infections- i was diagnosed as pre-diabetic & cut sugar our from my already low sugar diet. fast forward to january of this year i went to the er due to pain from another torsion on the right side & again the ovary was saved. i was put on ortho tricyclen lo & still have my iud & take the spironolactone but had horribly painful cysts last month which brought me to the er but with no torsion they did nothing. the pain has been intermitten since & is getting more severe. it feels like ice cubes in my ovaries & warm water/electic shocks down my thighs. i had the hpv vaccine but my last pap showed up irregular & the biopsy of cysts got lost. any thoughts on what happening?",
    "url": "http://ehealthforum.com/health/pcos-one-ovary-after-torsion-severe-pain-t479678.html",
    "tags": [
      "hair loss",
      "diet",
      "acne",
      "ovulation and ovaries"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "i am glad to help you out. this is not possible scientifically for a woman not to know and still be pregnant throughout the pregnancy. it is also not possible for the periods to continue and still be pregnant. the confirmation can be done by doing a urine pregnancy test or an ultrasound abdomen. the story of \u00e2\u0080\u009ci didn\u00e2\u0080\u0099t know i was pregnant\u00e2\u0080\u009d seems more like a fiction and less like a reality. i sincerely hope that helps. take care.",
    "question": "i was wanting to know if you could tell me if its possible for a woman to go through all their pregnancy without knowing they are pregnant and have periods and ngative pregnancy tests? iwas watching the show called \"i didnt know i was pregnant\" and wanted to know how real and accurate this show is and how somthing like that could happen?",
    "url": "http://ehealthforum.com/health/not-knowing-you-are-pregnant-t233897-a1.html",
    "tags": [
      "am i pregnant",
      "pregnant",
      "urine pregnancy test",
      "ultrasound",
      "pregnancy",
      "abdomen",
      "periods",
      "woman",
      "urine",
      "accurate pregnancy tests",
      "womens chat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "you are not alone. you should consider expert help from medical professionals who specialize in drug treatment. there are specialists who can counsel you during your detoxification from narcotics and provide medical assistance during this process. also you can call a drug or alcohol helpline to identify treatment centers in your area. treatment centers medically intake patients for as long as is necessary for you to understand the disease of drug addiction learn preventative measures to counter the disease and develop belief that there is life after methadone and oxycotin. further you may need the support of your friends family and a 12-step support group to fully recover from your addiction. simply to recover from addiction you need a willingness to change your life and the humility to start to take suggestions. to save your life you can take action now.",
    "question": "i have been taking methadose and oxycotin illeagely for over a year now. i am now trying to quit. the withdrawls are the worst thing i have ever experienced. so i keep going back to get more. i have no insurance and i dont have the money to go to the e. r. is there any way i can ease the pain so i can get my life back in order. please help i dont know what to do.",
    "url": "http://ehealthforum.com/health/topic51352.html",
    "tags": [
      "addiction, recovery"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "it is difficult to analyse your situation without a physical examination and a psychiatric complete history. you might definitely benefit by consulting a psychiatrist who can help you properly in dealing with your problems and prescribe you medications if needed.",
    "question": "i need help i drink every night and think that it has something to do with my personal life and the way i deal with things. i used to love my job and the banter now they are making me feel down and worthless. my husband has been doing this for a while now and i really need some help to stop other people making me feel so useless and worthless.",
    "url": "http://ehealthforum.com/health/i-need-help-i-drink-every-night-t281246.html",
    "tags": [
      "depression",
      "addiction, recovery"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "given the description you could be experiencing mental dependency on narcotics. it doesn\u00e2\u0080\u0099t seem that you are physically dependent on narcotics currently. in time if you don\u00e2\u0080\u0099t stop abusing narcotics you may develop physical dependence of the drugs. mental and emotional dependence on drugs is defined as a need for narcotics to achieve pleasure. physically dependent addicts require narcotics to stay alive. you can ask for expert help from a mental health doctor for drug addiction treatment. many former addicts have also found a way to keep the \"mental withdrawal\" in control by joining support groups like narcotics anonymous or alcoholics anonymous. these groups advocate complete lifestyle and belief change in order to recover from addiction. you can visit their websites at www. na. org or www. alcoholics-anonymous. org to look for a meeting near you.",
    "question": "i have had a lot of trouble getting off of narcotics (percocet and morphine my knee surgeon would give me the percocet and my family dr would give me the morphine) but this time i have actually done it. my last time using it was on new years eve. physically i am fine. mentally though i keep getting cravings for it and i try to figure out how to get more. (surgeon said if i need some go to my family doctor. family doctor would not give me anymore due to asking for refills too soon after getting a rx. ) i then tell myself \"no\" and then remind myself how far i have come. my question is: how long will it take for the mental withdrawl to go away? i am getting scared that i may given into one of those cravings and go to a hospital to get some. any suggestions on how to deal with this would be greatly appreciated.",
    "url": "http://ehealthforum.com/health/topic84923.html",
    "tags": [
      "withdrawal",
      "narcotics",
      "drug addiction treatment",
      "alcoholics anonymous",
      "narcotics anonymous",
      "addiction treatment",
      "drug addiction",
      "mental health",
      "addiction",
      "treatment",
      "addiction, recovery"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "it does not take much force at all to crush the larynx. crushing the human throat takes roughly that same amount of pressure as crushing an empty soda container. this is why a move such as a throat gouge should never be used in a fight. the only time this kind of move should be used is if it is life or death. a hit to the throat can easily kill a person and is not to joked with. i hope this clears your doubts.",
    "question": "hi. my name is roberto writing from italy. i write here because i'd have a question i can't resolve in my hometown. let me introduce me: i'm a karate black belt and i like to study anatomy in order to be as more effective as i can. my question is about windpipe's rings resistance to pressure and/or strikes. in short i'd like to know how much it takes to crush/to flat trachea's cartilages with a sharp strike to the cervical part of the throat. thankyou for your attention and patience.",
    "url": "http://ehealthforum.com/health/clinical-trials-research-and-studies-question-t512894.html",
    "tags": [
      "clinical trials, research, and studies"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "medicines that contain iron like tonoferon usually causes black stool.",
    "question": "the stool color is black (not loose) - is the black color of stool due to any of the above medicines? being holiday can not consult doctor instantly",
    "url": "http://ehealthforum.com/health/topic124662.html",
    "tags": [
      "general community chat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "you are right but the body is not yours. its your wife decision plus a doctor's eyes are never perverted. they ccan't see an appealing body all they look for is a trouble if any. thats it. it's called patient doctor relationship you are not even a patient. medical ethics don't even let you in here. if you feel this way discuss it with your wife persuade her to get a female examiner. tou can't do that. get some couple therapy sessions if you can't figure it out. in us it works this way. had you been in some non us state or a muslim one it would have been not possible with out your consent. but free country right. i hope it helps. visit our health centre for further guidance. take care",
    "question": "why is it that the medical profession is so behind the times when it comes to considering the feelings of husbands as it pertains to their wive's medical care. i just recently learned about the exams my wife has been subjected to on a yearly basis (at least one of the following: pelvic exam pap smear breast exam). it depresses and angers me that a male physician can perform those exams without my consent. meanwhile the same doctor over the course of more than 10 years has never asked me to remove anything more than my shirt while she is asked to strip down every time she sees him. i think without the consent of both partners in a marriage that it should be illegal for an opposite sex health care professional to perform invasive exams of this nature. we're not talking about an emergency here and i feel that he has caused irreparable damage to our marriage and has taken something from me that i can't ever get back. what is your take on this?",
    "url": "http://ehealthforum.com/health/yearly-breast-and-pelvic-exams-without-my-consent-angry-t438493.html",
    "tags": [
      "breast",
      "angry",
      "health care",
      "pap smear",
      "female",
      "angers",
      "eyes",
      "male",
      "sex",
      "about health care",
      "general community chat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "sinemet is a combination of levodopa and carbidopa. this medicine is used for treating parkinson\u00e2\u0080\u0099s disease. the choice of medicine(s) and dosage is strongly individual. you can consult your neurologist on whether or not to start sinemet or wait and hold off.",
    "question": "is it best to start on sinemet or \"hold off\".",
    "url": "http://ehealthforum.com/health/topic54910.html",
    "tags": [
      "health insurance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "you need to confirm with your insurance provider regarding coverage of investigation and consultation charges during your trial period. if these investigations are covered by your insurance provider during the trial period then these would be done for you during your visit to emergency. if these investigations are required to be done immediately then the doctors in the emergency room will get these done (as based on your examination findings and current health status) and you need to pay for them yourself in case your insurance provider does not cover these. you need not have to convince them to get these done. take care.",
    "question": "i may need diagnostic testing and this time i have a trail period before i can get my health insurance. i would be a self-pay pt and fear the cost of such tests. if i go to an emergency room can i convince them to order mris cts without insurance if i am concerned? i am putting this off for as long as i can right now.",
    "url": "http://ehealthforum.com/health/may-need-diagnostic-testing-t268556-a1.html",
    "tags": [
      "period",
      "health care",
      "health insurance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "it seems you are suffering from reflux and gastritis which is a common issue after gall bladder removal. regarding the abnormal feeling it requires a clinical examination to comment regarding the exact cause. it might be that the incision site is healing which can cause some hardening of the involved and surrounding region. the simple measures that are likely to help you are- 1. certain foods such as cauliflower broccoli cabbage brussels sprouts and legumes (beans) may cause bloating and gassiness. 2. dietary fiber may lessen symptoms. you should drink plenty of water and avoid soda which may cause gas and abdominal discomfort. 3. you can use some over the counter drugs like pepto bismol or tums for symptomatic relief. consider visiting the treating surgeon once for evaluation. take care!",
    "question": "its been since august 15 2012 and i have had issues. the incision in my bellybutton keeps spliting open infection. my dr. told me no it is not infection! did nothing! everything i try to eat even (one) bite. it feels like a rubber band is snapping inside! when i sleep on my left side everything on the right settles i feel something moving! there is an egg sized (? ) in the center between my navel and ribs. what could possibly cause the snapping feeling and what could possibly be moving inside me? kind of freaked out especially when my dr. who is a ta says nothing is wrong. i was 110 when this all began i am under 100 lbs i am 5ft 5in and nothing tastes good smells good and i'm nausious all the time.",
    "url": "http://ehealthforum.com/health/incision-in-my-bellybutton-keeps-spliting-open-infection-t367934.html",
    "tags": [
      "bellybutton",
      "infection",
      "august",
      "sleep",
      "sleep disorders",
      "recovery & post-op"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "yes after the surgery any strenous activty including intercourse is to be avoided for a week to avoid any pressure in the sinuses as it can lead to bleeding. relax yourself as headache which is moderate in intensity could be present in some patients for several weeks following surgery. if you notice any other symptom as severe pain bleeding fever decrease in vision double vision then consider visiting your treating doctor immediately. avoid blowing your nose also for a week. take care!",
    "question": "hello i've had an endoscopic sinus surgery some days ago. my doctor didn't gave me any specific guidance and i've had sex with my wife from the 2nd day after surgery. i saw some websites which prohibited patients from strenuous activities as sex so i was wondering if it is so harmful? and if yes why? or it will just cause bleeding from sinuses? i have some kind of headaches now and i'm really worried so any help is so appreciated! thanks in advance for your attention!",
    "url": "http://ehealthforum.com/health/strenuous-activities-after-endoscopic-sinus-surgery-t357554.html",
    "tags": [
      "ear",
      "nose",
      "after surgery",
      "headaches",
      "surgery",
      "sex",
      "sinus surgery",
      "after sinus surgery",
      "nose  throat",
      "attention disorders",
      "recovery & post-op"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "abortion the clinical way of stopping an unplanned/unprepared/unhealthy pregnancy.",
    "question": "abortion benefits",
    "url": "http://ehealthforum.com/health/abortion-purpose-t351265.html",
    "tags": [
      "abortion debate",
      "pregnancy",
      "abortion pregnancy",
      "benefits of",
      "abortion debate"
    ]
  }
]
